PANKAJ TIWARI



CONTACT

- @ Pankajtiwari00@yahoo.com
- 9911905403
- H.104 B Chawala, Najafgarh

SKILLS

Sales and Marketing Creative thinking Excellent communicator Techinical skills Team work _ Target Driven Pro_Active approach. Self Motivated

LANGUAGES

HINDI ENGLISH

INTERESTS

Watching Movies
Interaction with New people

OBJECTIVE

To Secure a challenging position in a reputable organization to expand my learning, knowledge and skills, Highly Capable Marketing Manger 10 + Years of Experience leading new intiatives product awerness exponentially, performed extensive forecast, Influential growth strategist.

EXPERIENCE

NIBAV ELEVATORS PVT LTD

OCT 2022 - Working

Business Development Manager - Team Handling

Identity new business Opportunities - Always responsible for new market, industries and potential customer for our industry.

Developing business strategies - Work closely with Senior Management to develop business strategies that align with company's overall goal and objectives.

Building and Maintaining relationships - Establish and maintain relationship with Architects and potential customers, partner to expand the company network and customer base.

Negotiating deals and contracts - Negotiate and finalize deals and contract with clients and partners and always ensuring that they are mutually beneficial and meet the compa requirements.

Analyzing Market Trends - Always stay up to date with market trends and analyze competitors activities to help the company stay competitive and make informed business decisions.

Creating and developing presentations - Create and deliver presentations to potential clients partner, and highlighting the company's products services and capabilities.

Monitoring team and reporting progres - Monitoring and report on business development initiatives and provide regular update to Senior Management.

STONEX INDIA

28 Oct 2020 - 30 Sep 2022

Business development Manager

Managing North and west delhi Mirco Market.

Handling Architects, Builder, contractors and High End Clients.

Maintain relationship with Architects lobby to get bussiness on regular basis.

Following high end sites and architect to get more business.

Preouring new clients through direct contact or reffrences.

Reviewing clients feedback and implementing necessary actions.

Remaing in tune witj trends with consumption to ensure our offerings remain relevant.

KIXX MEDIA PVT

June 2017 - Sep 2020

Business Expansion & Market Research

Ensure Daily office operations are performed in seamless and efficient Manner.

Managing office equipment, organizing, Arranging coordinating for Meetings.

Diary Management, Travel Management and Management in Box.

Ensuring company policies are followed

Help to support new centre opening any pan india location.

Visit the property inspection to get it verified as per company norms.

MAX LIFE INSURANCE

Nov 2014 - Apr 2017

Senior Backend Associate

Handling customer queries received by Genral offices.

Amendment according to the customer request after inspection documents.

Maintain coordination with the otyer team to get rectified the documents.

Receiving transactions data on daily basis and Re-organised it for analysis as per SOP.

Coordinate with Internal team to rectifyy the documents.

CSAV

Jan 2012 - SEP 2014

Process Associate

Using oracle to connect with domestic and international vendors.

Coordinate with clients and vendors for verify to shipping Information.

Implementing specific vendor requirments.

Resolving vendor problem concerning codes issue.

Monitoring ghe invoices as if we found discripancy.

Activation and decativation of codes.

Ensuring to resolve the discrepany within TAT.

SERCO

Jan 2011 - DEC 2012

Relationship Officer - Amex Process

Cross Selling to Existing and Acquisitions of new customer.

Provide solutions to the customer Credit card need.

Prepare sales reports.

Reviews own performance and Target Accodingly on Monthly basis.

Daily to do list to work on.

EDUCATION

Jamia Hamdard University

2011

BBA

68%

CBSE

2007

12th Class

60%

CBSE

2005

10th Class

60%